

CONTACT

+94 070 5735 453

☑ jayithpasindu1994@gmail.com

Maharagama, Colombo, Srilanka

koraad.github.io/myportfolio/

donpasindujayith.is-great.net/

SKILLS

- Web Development
- Shopify and WordPress
- Improvisation
- Creative Design
- Online Marketing
- Content Creation
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving & Critical Thinking
- Photoshop
- Graphic Design with Canva
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

BENG (HONS) SOFTWARE ENGINEERING (READING)

University of Westminster, UK 2021 - 2024

HIGH SCHOOL (COMBINED MATHEMATICS)

Wesley College, Colombo 2000 - 2013

CURRICULUM VITAE

DON PASINDU

Web Developer/Online Marketer

OBJECTIVE

Seeking a responsible and challenging position in a growth oriented progressive organization where my Education, Knowledge & Talents will significantly contribute to the overall success of the organization and provide opportunities for my career growth.

PROFILE

I am Don Pasindu Jayith Korottage a creative Web Developer with 3 years of experience in website development, e-commerce and online marketing. Accompanied by strong creative and analytical skills. I am an out of the box thinker, and a team player with an eye for details, who never takes no for an answer.

PORTFOLIO

Checkout my personal portfolio in the following link koraad.github.io/myportfolio/ and https://donpasindujayith.is-great.net/

TOOLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs Basics, Python Basics, Java with OOP, VS Code, Github, Shopify, WordPress, Photoshop, Canva, Facebook Ads

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Personal Showcase Projects (checkout the portfolio)

2019 - Present

Created some personal projects with HTML,
 CSS and JavaScript which are aligned with
 real world web development projects.

EXTRA CURRICULAR

- Coached the Senior Badminton team of Wesley College, Colombo
 O9 (Assistant Badminton Coach)
- Captained the Badminton team of General Sir John Kotelawala
 Defense University (KDU)
- All Island Junior National
 Badminton Championship in
 2007,2009 and 2010 (Awarded by
 Sri Lanka Badminton Association)
- Captained the Senior Badminton team of Wesley College, Colombo 09
- Awarded many prizes and certificates at the Annual Inter-House Athletic Meet for 4x100Relay, 4x400Relay, 800 meters, 1500 meters

REFERENCE

MR. MUNESH DAVID

Group Chief Internal Auditor, Dialog Axiata PLC

No.57, Dharmapala Mawatha, Colombo 03, Srilanka.

- +94-077-7088-131
- +94-077-7332-206

Munesh.David@dialog.lk

MR. INDIKA LIYANAHEWAGE

General Manager – Human Resources, Eskimo Fashion No: 44/16. P.O Box 30,

No: 44/16. P.O Box 30 Negombo, Srilanka.

+94-077-3596-616

indika.liyanahewage@gmail.com

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

ONLINE MARKETING

My own e-commerce brands

2020 - Present

- Founded an Activewear e-commerce brand and a Jewelry e-commerce brand and registered my business under the name BODYJENE LLC in USA. (currently not in business)
- Checkout, Bodyjene Activewear Instagram Page https://www.instagram.com/bodyjene/
- Checkout, Stylish Extras Jewelry Instagram Page
 https://www.instagram.com/stylishextras/

OTHER EXPERIENCE

WNS GLOBAL SERVICES (PVT) LTD, SRILANKA Senior Associate - Quality Operations

Jan 2020-Feb 2020

 Involved in assurance of Quality of subordinates as a Team leader which involved checking the quality of Document Storage Process

HONG KONG & SHANGHAI CORPORATION (HSBC)-HDPL, SRI LANKA

Associate - Financial Crime Risk Operations

Nov 2018-Oct 2019

 Investigated Money Laundering in Department of Financial Crime Risk and Regulatory Compliance as a Financial Crime Compliance Executive.

SRI LANKA ARMY

Officer Cadet

Sep 2015-Nov 2018

 Involved in military exercises, Firing sessions, military tactics and strategies and other administrational work at Sri Lanka Army and followed a Biomedical Engineering Degree Program at General Sir John Kotelawala Defense University (KDU)